It's a clinic for skills.
How do we get skills better.
Sick skill to a healthy skill?
This looks very red to me. Oh.
The “E” security rating jumps out to me.
Bloodbath.
Very, very good explanation.
Yeah.
Now not only it will review it, it actually going to improve
all those items that he found and make it much better.
Right.
Let's see if that works.
Hello, and welcome to yet
another episode of this #skillsclinic.
Absolutely.
The first episode, it's, It's one of them.
It's one of those two, for sure.
The first one.
But anyway, what's what is special skills?
So the skills clinic is really about how we can go
about understanding how good a skill is and improving it.
It's a clinic for skills.
How do we get skills better.
From a sick skill to a healthy skill?
Because the problem is people who create skills typically don't
understand whether their skill is actually creating an impact.
And it's it's very much done through anecdotal evidence.
I think my skills working because it did this thing once,
and I assume it's doing it perfectly all the other times.
So that's what we're trying to debunk a little bit.
And we'll show how we can understand and make skills better. So.
This is we need to talk, yesterday at
Q con with, the one and only Patick Debois.
And we went through patterns of like, bad, context engineering.
One of them was, vibe eval.
Like, you evaluate your skill based on your gut feeling.
Okay. Exactly. That's nice if we can do better.
But before we get to do that,
before we get to that, there is one more thing that we can do.
We can actually give people an advice of how to even start.
Yep, yep.
Right.
So first of all, what skill is, skill is,
structured
process or context for your agent,
to do something in a repeatable way.
Typically markdown. It's play.
It's written in plain text, it's markdown.
And it's the the structure is interesting because it's, it's
a little bit of structure at the top.
And then it's pretty much unstructured after that
because you can essentially just write what you want.
And then it just sits there waiting.
And this is the key thing,
waiting for the agent to pick on it and use it when it feels like
it needs to use it, when it feels like it can't do things itself without needing
this, the skill to encourage it, to do things a certain way.
Right? Right.
And this is this is a big issue with with agent systems generally.
They're kind of overeager.
They will try to do stuff assuming that they know what you want the outcome to be.
Yeah.
So skill gives that a little bit
more of structure and process and algorithm of what we really do.
Let's let's see an example. Yeah.
So so what people usually do nowadays on the internet is when they want to their
AI to write an app, they're basically looking for a product.
To, to copy paste, to get ideas.
Let me show you.
I found one of those prompts online.
So let me open here in VSCode.
Here it is.
Right.
It's called express rest API generator.
Generate the rest API, rest API for it to do up.
So this is perfect.
Does it do it quickly or is it using the, express JavaScript server? It's
I think I have no idea.
Yeah, maybe, I suspect it's probably right here.
Express JS here.
I, I mean, I skimmed through it.
It looks very good.
It sounds like, it has a database layer
and, it has, like authentication.
What else it has here?
Design philosophy, which this is what I like.
Right.
It's kind of what, what I appreciate pragmatic simplicity.
This is great.
Flexible typing for TypeScript without fighting it.
A dynamic queries, building observability.
Like the real good stuff. Yeah, yeah, I liked it.
So I think what I'm going to do is,
I'm just going to ask, cloud code to implement it.
So, use of the, Uber prompt
from to
a create a to do to do app.
That's like what everybody use.
So we'll do it as well. The rest API.
And what do we need that authentication.
And what, what else.
Import export.
On top of our regular tasks
and things.
And Mark
complete right.
And yeah.
Whatever. Okay.
Let's see what, let's see what it does.
I'm in the approach was good.
So it should produce like a working out. You.
Now what I think
we should do is actually assess if it's good and or not.
And there are tools doing that.
One of them is, sonar.
Sonar. Cube sonar. Yep.
And it will give us an idea
whether the app that Cornwall will do is.
Now sonar cloud, tests quality as well as security.
Yes. Yeah.
So we got both which is, which is good.
That's exactly what we need. Right.
So it will install some dependencies and and build it.
So I think it's almost done actually because it's already built into it.
Yeah. Pretty good you know.
And so in fact it's yeah. Yeah. It's
doing the npm install.
You know, something failed.
It will fix it.
Cloud code is very smart.
Oh. There we go.
So let's bump in the.
Versions from very old one to a nice, nice, nice.
What else going on here?
And then we will actually commit and push. Yep.
And once this is done, we can connect sonar cube and and.
And so sonar cube, runs in the.
So you said sorry clean club.
So you commit it and push it and then it's running on the,
on the, on the pull request or or you run it like if.
You review that, look at that.
Yeah. Yep.
Excellent. One minute 36 seconds 36.
And then towards the loop of the running dependency.
So it's around a minute. Yeah. Amazing. All right.
Commitment push.
And once we have it in my GitHub we can go ahead and connect.
So. Yep.
Okay.
Pop pop pop pop pop pop pop.
Get and and.
Okay. Pushed.
Yeah. Pushed. Okay.
So the cloud should pick it up.
Let's see if we have it configured.
Otherwise, the project,
What is it?
That's a demo.
That's a little. Here we go.
A little demo set up and, previous version.
I guess.
Great project.
Let's just make sure
that it is picking up what we need.
We do it in,
what is it?
Announcement here.
Automatic analysis.
Up, I guess.
Let's see if that actually works.
Oh, okay. All right, all right.
This looks very red to me. Oh.
The “E” security rating jumps out to me.
Significant. Oh, yeah. Well that's your. Yeah.
Security background.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Blockers a lot. All the red.
This is not great.
This is not great okay.
First of all we want to improve it.
And and as we said, it's probably worth converting
into skill and see if we can, like, see if our skill is good.
So first of all, we need to, get the sonar, finished.
And can you see the results?
Let's see if we can get the results into into our Claude.
Yeah. Because this is how we can make the raid. Yep.
So it's pulling that and it's pulling out. Oh.
It's okay.
It's got the MCP connection into Circe.
Yep. Gotcha.
Okay. So.
Yeah. Project. Okay. Great.
Bloodbath.
Very, very good explanation.
Yeah. Okay.
So here is the summary.
And, 43 issues,
five security hot, both 48 findings total.
Okay. Not great, not great.
So, you basically to make
it any prompt a skill, all we
need to do is add a tiny bit of metadata upfront.
Right.
So, we end Yaml to markdown
because this is what our industry now.
It's terrible.
And we need two fields. Right.
The name I'm going to be very creative.
And end the description.
As a proper lazy developer, I'm going to copy
the name to the description because who cares.
We'll see, we'll see.
Who cares?
Yeah.
All right.
Okay, so no, we I think we have a skill.
Oh, and we can rename it to skill, I guess.
Right.
Skill, M.D..
Yeah.
G was renamed Q
skill, and you skill him.
You're an exists. We don't need to use.
So I'm going to delete this one because we don't need to.
And name it again.
Do you want, skill. I,
I just announced that disk. Yep.
I can see that. Yeah. Okay.
What we can do in order to know not when we are in skill territory.
Yeah.
We can already start making some, checks.
Right.
So, we can do it from code line.
We can do it from cloud code.
Let's do it from command line.
For for DevOps.
So, skill review,
skill.
Now, the review is an interesting one because of the review.
What the review does is it essentially determines,
how good the skill is, not in terms of the impact it's making,
but the quality of how that skill has been written.
Right.
It sounds to me like a unit test.
It's very similar. Yeah, yeah.
Well, look at the skill itself and tell us whether it's structurally correct. Yes.
And where were the actually okay.
So average score 37. Not great.
Not great.
No. Not good.
Not good at all. Let's see what happens.
So validation check pass because well I have name and description.
But the judge evaluation is terrible.
So description is very bad.
23 now this is where what you mentioned
the importance of the description comes in.
So there are three parts that are critical
for a good description specificity.
Mine is not very specific. Yeah.
What does it mean. Express
meter.
Completeness to describe what it does.
Again like definitely not there.
And activation whereas activation conflict
risk conflict reasons about if I have two skills
that both mentioned express or sleepy
generator which one is the agent.
And that's, that's the key piece.
Which one should the agent pick. Right.
Because this is what the description
is is, is providing the agent with the information.
The agent reads the description in the name. Yep.
Before it loads the full skill and it loads it based on if it thinks that
the task it's trying to complete, it requires that skill for.
So this is actually you mentioned activation.
This is actually a key piece of the activation
because this is what this is the information
it has to determine whether it should activate it or not.
Or this one or any other. Yeah. Exactly.
Exactly. Right.
And then our judge, which is the LM right.
We run clock tool to evaluate it, makes
says okay, well
you have the content is moderately efficient and,
and the content is organized into logical sessions.
Great.
This is why I will give you 52 and not zero.
Yeah, but but first of all, the content is not great.
But second, this skill provides actionable executable code
but teaches extremely dangerous security. And.
And that's exactly what's on our shoulders.
Yes. Right.
So we can use our judge to optimize it.
And the way we do it is there's
this optimize.
Yeah.
Seems simple. Enough.
Once we asked our judge to optimize it.
Now not only it will review it, it actually going to improve
all those items that he found and make it much better.
Right. Let's see if that works.
So this is using another LMS to make suggestions.
And this is a very uncommon practice.
Yeah. In data engineering.
And it's called dilemmas A judge. Yeah.
And, and uses another instance of an alum or another model
or but just like outsider view
to actually improve what the other did.
Well in our case it's improving what someone else did. Yep.
Okay.
This can take up to one minute is about like I really.
Yeah I.
All right. So, here are the results.
Diff.
Okay.
There is, a lot of fixes, I suppose.
A lot of fixes.
Well, it definitely does change. In quite a lot.
It deserves a lot of fixes.
So yeah, the diff is everything.
Some changes removed to description. Non,
instructional phases and all code examples.
Description was left unchanged as the review.
Right. Did what. Okay.
The review all to do exemplary and apply those changes.
Yes. Apply those changes score from 50% to 90%.
Very nice 40% improvement after three iterations.
Yeah. Actually did three dimensions.
Let's do review again and see what it thinks now okay.
So it says 90. This is 89.
That's the that's the nondeterminism of.
The math work. Yes.
So but yeah we got much better.
Description is not 100%. Yeah.
Reviews and and the content is now 77%, which is also pretty good.
Okay. Yeah. Can go higher, but I think it's good.
Look at the changes. The description did change.
Wow. Did.
Okay.
So no, it is much richer.
Yeah.
It actually mentions all the keywords that will help with.
The activation for the new agent. Yeah.
And and the workflow now, changed dramatically.
We have a set up and other examples and obviously those examples are
with all
the learnings about the anti-patterns.
All right.
So what we're going gonna try now is generate exactly the same up.
Yeah. Now here's the interesting part.
What we did now with evolve was improving.
The future code. Yeah.
Before the code was actually written.
We have here not a guarantee, but a promise, that
the code that we are going to write will actually be good.
So this is kind of, you know, shift left.
Yeah, yeah.
So from checking what's going on in production to checking in CI
to checking in the code, now we are in,
negative territory.
We are,
we are checking the future code that.
Yeah, doesn't even exist.
Yeah, this is in the brain of the lamb.
That it will help.
Oh, well. Even works.
That would be pretty cool.
Okay, so now when we have a skill,
we can actually pack it as the context artifact.
Yeah.
In, Tesla tile or Tesla plugin.
Same thing. Right.
So how do we do it.
We have a skill for that. Yep. Yep.
So we can say install a skill
and a tile create or skill from the self registry.
so we can install and skill. Yeah.
That will create a tile or a plugin from, from the skill as a package of BLE.
Context artifact.
Right.
So the tile create or installed
and next step convert it will be prompt in the proper tile. No.
We now have a skill,
improved and fixed back.
It and it's called skill. And,
into a tile.
So a tile is actually a little bit similar to a plugin, right?
In the sense that it can contain context.
One of those pieces of context is skill.
And so what we're gonna do now do is turn this skill and into a bigger tile.
So it's essentially packaged
into something called a tile, which can contain other context.
In this case it will just contain the skill.
But it also can contain multiple skills.
You can. Yeah. And rules. Yes.
And what are rules?
Rules are rules are interesting.
So the way that skills almost like
not lazy loaded but loaded when they What suppose it is lazy loaded, isn't it?
It's loaded at the last moment when the agent thinks it needs to to
to to read it.
A rule is something which is kind of like more added
into the agent MD or the code MD, whereby it's
absolutely text that the agent needs to read every single time.
It's something that needs to be part of the core,
you know, definition of how agents do things.
You've got to be a little bit careful of rules in the sense
of if you bloat, too many rules in the, in the in the agent.
All of a sudden, you start running out of context.
That's one of the key things,
but a skill, kind of is nice for all, because you don't load all skills at once.
You load it when you need to. So you've got to be a little bit careful.
So there is a there is a little bit. Of a difference.
Yeah. All right. So let's see what it did.
So this is by the way
the title Json is the metadata of the tiles that we have installed. Yep.
And we have here our a tile creator skill.
But we also created the, our skill.
Here is it's Tile Express API generator. Yep.
And this is in style Json.
Now look what Claude did.
It not only created the skill.
Yeah. It also created some rules.
Interesting security rule is exactly what you mentioned. Yep.
And that's a list of all those terrible things.
Not, learned from sonar. Absolutely.
And this is interesting
because these are the things we've got to be very, very careful with.
Not pollute, not putting too, too much in here.
And this is this is nice.
This is concise.
This is short.
Whereas the skill will be much longer.
And only when we need to do that certain thing will load it.
Whereas this, this is core information that we should be doing every single time
when generating any code. Yep.
So what we can do is something like, publish it
to decimal register.
And install it locally for you to use.
We want both,
and section.
It says here okay, three fun 367 front loaded tokens.
Nice. Okay.
And it's pulling this because it's running Tesla in the background.
It's all this is Tesla data that it's kind of like pulling and sharing with the
with the client okay.
So now it is both installed
and published or other people can use it at least in my workspace or yep, public.
This is private but it can be public.
I don't think you need to recycle the, let's clear.
To pick it up, I see. Oh.
I don't know.
I think you can maybe even type in slash filter
by the name of skill, and it will see if it has it or not.
Not we can do it anyway.
Yeah.
Just to make sure.
Okay.
That's ready. Okay.
Regenerate.
Was the was the type you know the
the whole like I think was invented for me.
For typos for, for typos.
So yeah. So it picks up everything.
It doesn't care about typos.
This is so much better than the command line. Yeah.
Which you have very be very. Yeah.
Okay. Follow the skill patterns.
Look at that.
Now it's going to rewrite everything.
Look. Secrets. Yeah.
That will that didn't happen because hardcoded passwords and stuff.
This is very cool
okay.
This also should take like two minutes.
I love yellow mode.
Yeah.
Oh that's that's the best option for sure.
And we we can trust it. Yeah.
Oh yeah. Oh, man, I know that.
Not nothing on my machine that would be,
Well, I mean, this
what can possibly go wrong.
Yeah.
okay. So it's done. All right. It's doing is done.
The npm install. Build.
Wow. That was even faster.
I think.
The build failed again.
That's consistent.
The first build.
G if it had just been plain text it been fun.
Oh yeah.
Oh actually does that thing okay.
Build a clean one means 37 seconds okay.
Yes yes you're right, you're right. Okay.
Undo it for so. No
okay.
Let's see what are some other things now.
Okay.
Post waiting for someone to pick it up.
Let me know when it's done. Oh, faults.
And what we need to do is we need to go here
and see if we have analysis in progress.
And we do. Excellent.
It will take
a minute and we will eagerly refresh a little.
Probably shouldn't.
But, you know, we can never trust.
Okay, what's going on now?
Okay.
We went from what it was.
Was it 19 or something? Yeah.
To actually just to one.
And this one is SQL queries.
Oh okay.
It still does the SQL queries but that's like
that's an amazing improvement.
What do we ask. Let's ask.
Oh wow. There you go. So you got a history.
Yeah 25 down to we.
Went to like month stability issues to whatever you know.
But you can get a from F so.
25 down to eight maintainability issues.
And let's see what it's going on now
this is an amazing improvement.
And we can just go ahead and try to do better.
Yeah.
Now one of the reasons we still have one issue
is because remember how we created the skill.
Yeah we created it just based on what we think will work.
And we did unit testing.
Right.
And the unit testing showed real issues and that was our review. Yep.
But we can actually do better.
We can do more of an end to end testing of the skill.
Yes. Again, before the writing code
we did here, what we did here is, is we tested in production.
Yep, yep.
We generated the code and looked if the code is good.
Yeah. So that's a production of the AI model.
So the production of our, software delivery.
But we kind of tested in production.
And we shouldn't do that.
We actually do should do tests on our skill before the code is generally. Yes.
And that's our next step. Yes.
And this is the task evals.
So task evals are about we talked about the quality of the of the skill.
This is all about how it's written thinking about best practices of how
skills are written a task eval is about identifying
the impact of of a of a skill.
This is running an LLM with without the skill and identifying,
whether the, whether the task was completed better
because the skill was there or has it actually regressed?
How much better are there things we can improve?
So the idea is we create scenarios each with, evaluation criteria,
and we are scored based on the results, based based on what is created afterwards.
If that's if that's great, we get 100%.
If it's not, we get far, far lower.
And you can identify how to improve your skill based on the results
that you get back.
And this is going to what we're going to do next.
Absolutely.
On the same project we want to get to zero issues.
Absolutely. We're close but not there. We'll see if it was helpful.
Sounds good.
Stay tuned to the next episode of Hashtag Skills Clinic.
Bye for now.